Finding Aid for Hunein F. Maassab papers, 1951-2002
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Publications, 1954-1999
  - 1984-1989
    - Biological Characteristics of a Cold-Adapted Influenza A Virus Mutation Residing on a Polymerase Gene, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Resolution of a Common RNA Sequencing Ambiguity by Terminal Deoxynucleotidyl Transferase, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Prospects for Influenza Type B Live Attenuated Vaccines, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Restricted Replication of a Cold-Adapted Reassortant Influenza A Virus in the Lower Respiratory Tract of Chimpanzees, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Biological Characterization and Sequence Analysis of Type-B Cold Reassortant Genes in Vaccine Development, 1986 (Box 9)
    - The Role of Specific Genes from Cold-Adapted A and B 'Master' Strains in Conferring Phenotypic and Genetic Markers of Attenuation to Candidate Vaccine Reassortants, 1987 (Box 9)
    - Genetics of Cold-Adapted B/Ann Arbor/1/66 Influenza Virus Reassortants: The Acidic Polymerase (PA) Protein Gene Confers Temperature Sensitivity and Attenuated Virulence, 1987 (Box 9)
    - Nucleotide Sequences of the PA and PB1 Genes of B/Ann Arbor/1/66 Virus: Comparison with Genes of B/Lee/50 and Type A Influenza Viruses, 1987 (Box 9)
    - A Mutation in the PA Protein Gene of Cold-Adapted B/Ann Arbor/1/66 Influenza Virus Associated with Reversion of Temperature Sensitivity and Attenuated Virulence, 1987 (Box 9)
    - Analysis of Virus and Host Factors in a Study of A/Peking/2/79 (H3N2) Cold-Adapted Vaccine Recombinant in which Vaccine-Associated Illness Occurred in Normal Volunteers, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Identification of Four Genes that Attenuate Influenza A/Ann Arbor/6/60 (H2N2) Cold-Adapted Reassortant Viruses, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Identification of Sequence Changes in the Cold-Adapted, Live Attenuated Influenza Vaccine Strain, A/Ann Arbor/6/60 (H2N2), 1988 (Box 9)
    - Characteristics of a Persistent Infection in Madin-Darby Canine Kidney Cells with Influenza Virus C, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Live Influenza Virus Vaccine, Chapter 20 of Vaccines, Plotkin and Mortimer, Eds., 1988 (Box 9)
    - Comparison of Live, Attenuated H1N1 and H3N2 Cold-Adapted and Avian-Human Influenza A Reassortant Viruses and Inactivated Virus Vaccine in Adults, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Tissue Destruction Resulting from the Interaction of Cytotoxic T Cells and Their Targets, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Sequence Comparison of Wild-Type and Cold-Adapted B/Ann Arbor/1/66 Influenza Virus Genes, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Ultrastructural Localization of Viral Nucleic Acid by In Situ Hybridization, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Four Viral Genes Independently Contribute to Attenuation of Live Influenza A/Ann Arbor/6/60 (H2N2) Cold-Adapted Reassortant Virus Vaccines, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Evaluation of Cold-Recombinant Influenza A/Korea (CR-59) Virus Vaccine in Infants, 1989 (Box 9)
    - Attenuation and Phenotypic Stability of Influenza B/Texas/1/84 Cold Adapted Reassortant Virus: Studies in Hamsters and Chimpanzees, 1989 (Box 9)
    - Origin of ts Phenotype Expression of Cold-Adapted Influenza Virus A/AA/6/60, 1989 (Box 9)
    - Ultrastructural Localization of Herpes Simplex Virus RNA by In Situ Hybridization, 1989 (Box 9)
  - 1990-1994
    - A 36-Nucleotide Deletion Mutation in the Coding Region of the NS1 Gene of AN Influenza A Virus RNA Segment 8 Specifies A Temperature-Dependent Host Range Phenotype, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Cold-Adapted Influenza Viruses for Use as Live Vaccines for Man, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Evaluation of the Infectivity, Immunogenicity, and Efficacy of Live Cold-Adapted Influenza B/Ann Arbor/1/86 Reassortment Virus Vaccine in Adults, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Differential Interaction of Virulent and Attenuated Influenza Virus Strains with Ferret Alveolar Macrophages: Possible Role in Pathogenicity, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Laboratory Properties of Cold-Adapted (c.a.) Influenza B Live Vaccine Strains Developed in the US and USSR, and their B/Ann Arbor/1/86 ca Reassortant Vaccine Candidates, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Detection of Toxic Viral-Associated Double-Stranded RNA (dsRNA) in Influenza-Infected Lung, 1991 (Box 9)
    - Dominant-Negative Mutants as Antiviral Agents: Simultaneous Infection with the Cold-Adapted Live-Virus Vaccine for Influenza A Protects Ferrets from Disease Produced by Wild-Type Influenza A, 1991 (Box 9)
    - New Aspects of Influenza Viruses, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Detect Virus Activity with a Biofilm Sensor, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Development of Attenuated Live Respiratory Virus Vaccines: Progress Toward the Use of Live Cold-Adapted Influenza Vaccine in Man, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Immunization of Infants and Young Children with Live Attenuated Trivalent Cold-Recombinant Influenza A H1N1, H3N2, and B Vaccine, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Evaluation of a Cold-Adapted Influenza B/Texas/84 Reassortment Virus (CRB-87) Vaccine in Young Children, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Trivalent Cold-Adapted Influenza Virus Vaccine: Evidence for Virus in Susceptible Adults, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Molecular and Biological Changes in the Cold-Adapted 'Master Strain' A/Aa/6/60 (H2N2) Influenza Virus, 1993 (Box 9)
    - Immunization of Institutionalized Asthmatic Children and Patients with Psychomotor Retardation Using Live Attenuated Cold-Adapted Reassortment Influenza A H1N1, H3N2 and B Vaccines, 1993 (Box 9)
    - A Persistent Infection in MDCK Cells by an Influenza Type B Virus, 1993 (Box 9)
    - Variability in Infectivity of CR Influenza Vaccines in Humans, 1993 (Box 9)
    - Trivalent Cold Recombinant Influenza Live Vaccine in Institutionalized Children with Bronchial Asthma and Patients with Psychomotor Retardation, 1993 (Box 9)
  - 1995-1999
    - Prevention of Influenza by the Intranasal Administration of Cold-Recombinant, Live-Attenuated Influenza Virus Vaccine: Importance of Interferon-? Production and Local IgA Response, 1995 (Box 9)
    - Cytokines and the Acute Phase Response to Influenza Virus in Mice, 1995 (Box 9)
    - Gene Analysis of Reassortant Influenza Virus by RT-PCR Followed by Restriction Enzyme Digestion, 1996 (Box 9)
    - Evaluation of Candidate Strains of Live-Attenuated Respiratory Syncytial Virus (RSV) for Human Vaccine, 1996 (Box 9)
    - Phenotypic Characteristics of A/AA/6/60 Viruses and Reassortants, 1996 (Box 9)
    - Sequence Comparisons of A/AA/6/60 Influenza Viruses: Mutations Which May Contribute to Attenuation, 1996 (Box 9)
    - Chemokine Profile in MRC5 Cells Infected with Respiratory Syncytial Virus (RSV), 1997 (Box 9)
      (abstract and presentation slides only)
    - The Cell Receptor Level is Reduced During Persistent Infection with Influenza Virus C, 1997 (Box 9)
    - Studies in the Development of Live Attenuated Cold-Adapted Influenza Virus Vaccine for Humans, 1997 (Box 9)
    - The Role of Respiratory Syncytial Virus (RSV) in Exacerbation of Airway Reactivity, circa 1997 (Box 9)
    - Principle of Cold-Adaptation in the Derivation of Live Attenuated Respiratory Virus Vaccines, Chapter in Biotechnological Applications of Cold-Adapted Organisms, 1998.
    - IL-12 cDNA Skin Transfection Potentiates Human Papillomavirus E6 DNA Vaccine-Induced Antitumor Immune Response, 1998 (Box 9)
    - Immunological Properties of Plaque Purified Strains of Live Attenuated Respiratory Syncytial Virus (RSV) for Human Vaccine, 1999 (Box 9)
    - Live Influenza Virus Vaccine, Chapter in 3rd edition of Vaccines, 1999 (Box 9)
  - Undated
    - Miscellaneous Abstracts, undated (Box 9)
    - Attenuation of Influenza Viruses for Man by Adaptation to Growth at Low Temperatures, undated (Box 9)
    - Characteristics of a Persisting Filterable Agent in a Continuous Culture Derived from Embryonic Mouse Tissue, undated (Box 9)
    - Development and Characteristics of Cold-Adapted Reassortant Vaccines to Type A and to Type B Influenza Viruses for Use in Man, undated (Box 9)
    - Development and Characterization of Attenuated Respiratory Viruses for Use as Live Virus Vaccine for Man, undated (Box 9)
    - Development of a 'Master' Strain A/AA/6/60 -- H2N2 Of Type A Influenza Virus as a Donor for Use in Live Virus Vaccine in Man, undated (Box 9)
    - Evaluation in Children of Cold Adapted (CA) Influenza B Live Attenuated Intranasal Vaccine Prepared by Reassortment Between Wild-Type B/Ann Arbor/1/86 and CA B/Leningrad/14/55 Viruses, undated (Box 9)
    - Five-Season Evaluation of Cold-Adapted Live Influenza Virus Vaccines Among Japanese Volunteers against Natural Epidemics, undated (Box 9)
      (conference paper)
    - Genes Associated with Virulence of Mouse Adapted Variants of Influenza A/Ann Arbor/6/60 (H2N2) Virus, undated (Box 9)
    - Principle of Cold-Adaptation in the Derivation of Live Attenuated Respiratory Virus Vaccines, undated (Box 9)
    - Recombinant B/14/51/1 of B/Ann Arbor/2/86 and Cold-Adapted Donor of Attenuation B/Leningrad/14/17/55: Preparation and Laboratory Properties of Cold-Adapted Donor and Recombinant, undated (Box 9)
    - Second Generation Cold Adapted Influenza Vaccines, undated (Box 9)
    - Sequence Changes in Four Genes Associated with Attenuation of the Cold-Adapted A/AA/6/60 (H2N2) Influenza Virus 'Master Strain,', undated (Box 9)
    - [Miscellaneous Writings on HeLa Cells], undated (Box 9)
    - [Summary for Francis of Recombination Studies in Animal Viruses], undated (Box 9)
    - [Theory of Viral Infection], undated (Box 9)
    - [Use of HeLa Cells for Viral Synthesis], undated (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous Handwritten Drafts and Notes, undated (Box 10)
- Research, 1951-1999
  Research, 1951-1999 comprises records related to Maassab's research in the Department of Epidemiology at the University of Michigan's School of Public Health. The first two subseries, Budgets and Proposals, Contracts and Reports, relate to the funding and administration of his research. Laboratory Procedures includes notebooks and documents used in Maassab's laboratory to teach and remind researchers of standard procedures, recipes and protocols. The subseries Virus Inventories and Passage Histories comprises lists of viruses stored, used and shared by the laboratory, along with histories of several of the more important viruses. Laboratory Notebooks and Data is the largest subseries, and comprises numerous series of binders and notebooks that record Maassab's research. Most of this subseries was originally stored in three-ring binders. During processing, the binders were removed, but their labels were recorded on the folders to which the materials were transferred, and whenever possible, the binder labels were removed and placed in the front of the folders. A number of boxes in this subseries are restricted from researcher use because they contain documents, usually related to sera collection or vaccine trials, that link individual names with sensitive medical information.
  - Budgets
    - Aviron, 1998 (Box 10)
    - Clinical Virology Laboratory, 1984; 1989 (Box 10)
    - Department of Health and Human Services, 1984-1985 (Box 10)
    - Department of Health and Human Services Projects, 1984-1990; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Maassab-Project Budget Reports, 1989-1993; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous Budgets and Contracts, 1981-1989 (Box 10)
    - National Institute of Health, 1984-1986 (Box 10)
    - Pasteur Merieux, 1993-1998 (Box 10)
    - Proposed Expenditures, 1984-1992 (Box 10)
    - Shaman Pharmaceuticals, Inc., 1992-1993 (Box 10)
    - Travel and Hosting Expense Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 10)
    - Virus Laboratory, 1984; 1989; 1998 (Box 10)
  - Meetings, Proposals and Reports
    - Meetings
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 10)
      - National Institute of Health (NIH) Meeting Summaries, 1976-1986; 7 folders (Box 10)
    - Proposals, undated; 1972-1997; 29 folders (Box 11)
    - Reports
      - Annual Progress Reports, 1966-1982; 15 folders (Box 11)
      - Annual Progress Reports, September 1987-June 1993; 10 folders (Box 12)
      - Ferret Studies, Series II, May 1995 (Box 12)
      - Final Reports, 1977-1993; 4 folders (Box 12)
      - Progress Reports, undated; 1980-1995; 13 folders (Box 12)
      - Quarterly Progress Reports, June 1974 (Box 12)
      - Research Reports, undated; 1993; 3 folders (Box 12)
      - Semi-Annual Reports, October 1986-April 1992; 7 folders (Box 12)
  - Laboratory Procedures
    - "Recipes -- Maassab's Kitchen,", undated (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous Procedures, undated (Box 13)
    - Procedures I, undated; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - I Procedures, undated (Box 13)
    - Procedures II, undated; 1 notebook (Box 13)
    - Procedures II, undated; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Procedures, undated; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Class Procedures, undated (Box 13)
    - Acute Respiratory Disease Study, Blank Case History and Consent Forms, undated (Box 13)
    - IaI Procedures, 1964-1965; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - [Untitled Notebook], 1977-1978 (Box 13)
    - Respiratory Virus Surveillance Procedures, 1978 (Box 13)
    - Notes on ELISA Protocol, circa 1987 (Box 13)
    - Procedures for Virus Purification, 1988 (Box 13)
    - Tissue Cell Lines, 1988-1991 (Box 13)
    - Hamster Trivalent Vaccine Study Protocol, 1990 (Box 13)
    - Protein Gels, circa 1992 (Box 13)
    - Primary Chick Lung Experiments, 1993 (Box 13)
    - Protocol for the Production, Safety Testing and Characterization of Cold-Adapted Influenza Virus Reassortant Vaccine Pools, 1993 (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous Protocols and Procedures, 1995; undated (Box 13)
  - Virus Inventories and Passage Histories
    - Minuse Virus Catalogue and Information, 1931-1977 (Box 13)
    - Influenza Strains, 1938-1978 (Box 13)
    - Virus Passage, 1959-1961 (Box 13)
    - Assorted Virus Pools, 1965-1991 (Box 13)
    - Location Guide, circa 1975-1978 (Box 14)
    - Freezer Lists, 1976-1978 (Box 14)
    - Freezer Log, circa 1979 (Box 14)
    - Record of Virus Stock at-70°, circa 1979-1980 (Box 14)
    - Viruses Given to Dr. Dan DeBorde & Mrs. Louise Allen & Passages of PDII, circa 1979-1983 (Box 14)
    - Passage History and Update of Material in Freezer, 1987 (Box 14)
    - Freezer Inventory, 1988 (Box 14)
    - Freezer 1, circa 1992 (Box 14)
    - Viruses Sent and Received, 1995-1997 (Box 14)
    - History of the Cold-Adapted 'Master Strain' A/Ann Arbor/6/60-H2N2, undated (Box 14)
    - History of Miscellaneous Viruses, undated (Box 14)
    - Handwritten Inventory Lists, undated (Box 14)
    - Miscellaneous lists, undated; 5 folders (Box 14)
  - Laboratory Notebooks and Data
    - Numbered 3-Ring Binders (Box 15)
      - I: Fabish Before, 1957 undated (Box 15)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2068 ]
      - II: Tests, 1957-1959; 2 folders (Box 15)
      - IIII: Serology, 1963; 2 folders (Box 15)
      - IV: E. Minuse Equine Influenza, 1963; 2 folders (Box 15)
      - V: Dagmar Kunert, 1963-1964; 2 folders (Box 15)
      - VI: Dagmar Kunert, 1964; 2 folders (Box 15)
      - VII: Dagmar Kunert, 1965 (Box 15)
      - VIII: Herlocher 1, 1964-1965; 2 folders (Box 15)
      - IX: Herlocher 2, undated (Box 15)
      - X: Bessie Ling, 1965-1966 (Box 15)
      - XI: Avian, 1966-1968 (Box 15)
      - XII: [Untitled], 1965-1968; 2 folders (Box 16)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2078 ]
      - XIII: X-15, 1968-1972 (Box 16)
      - XIV: Hong Kong Flu, 1968; 2 folders (Box 16)
      - XV: Julie and Sue, 1966-1970; 2 folders (Box 16)
      - XVI: Tests, 1969; 1969-1971; 2 folders (Box 16)
      - XVII: Nasal Vaccine Study, 1968-1972; 2 folders (Box 16)
      - XVII: [Untitled], 1973-1984; 2 folders (Box 16)
      - XIX: HI's (Hemagglutination Inhibition Tests), 1985-1997; 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Sera Collections
      - Acute Respiratory Disease Study, University Health Service, 1951-1978; 2 folders (Box 17)
        (see also Box 14)
      - Serology Collection, 1966 (Box 17)
      - Serology Collection: University Hospital, 1966; 1969; 2 folders (Box 17)
      - Hospital Collection Pools and Chart, 1969 (Box 17)
    - RNA Experiments
      - Influenza RNA Experiment and Daily Logbook, 1964-1966 (Box 17)
      - Influenza RNA Notes, 1961-1977 (Box 17)
      - 1977-1981, 1990-1991; 2 volumes (Box 17)
    - 5-FU (5-fluorouracil Tests)
      - Loose Notes and Data, 1962 (Box 17)
      - Books I-XI and XN, 1962-1983; 7 volumes in 5 folders (Box 17)
    - Photometric Tests
      - HI Book I: Drescher Tests, Milford Equine Study, Hennessy and Allen, Duck/Eng/62, 1965-1968; 3 folders (Box 17)
      - HI Book II, 1969; 3 folders (Box 17)
      - HA Book PIII: Drescher Tests, Louise Allen, 1964-1967; 2 folders (Box 17)
      - HA Book PIV, 1967-1969; 2 folders (Box 18)
      - HI Book PV, 1970; 3 folders (Box 18)
      - Book PVI: Miller Trials, 1967 (Box 18)
      - Book PVII, undated; 3 folders (Box 18)
    - HI (Hemagglutination Inhibition)
      - AA/CR13-AA/CR33, 1971-1978; 2 folders (Box 18)
      - AA/CR37-AA/CR49., 1979-1980 (Box 18)
      - HI Experiment Data, 1987-1988 (Box 18)
    - Plaque Books
      - I-VII, 1968-1980; 3 folders (Box 18)
      - VIII-XLV, 1981-1990; 8 folders (Box 19)
      - Kilbourne and BBL, P.A., 1990-1995; 3 folders (Box 20)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2074 ]
    - Neuraminidase Inhibition (NI) Tests
      - Neuraminidase Determination Standardization, 1972-1978; 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Neuraminidase Standardization and Inhibition, 1972 (Box 20)
      - Book I: Instructions and Standardizations, 1971 (Box 20)
      - Book II: Rose, Baker and Keesler Pools, Ferret and Rabbit Sera, X-15, X-15 (HK), AA-183, Sing, HK, Aichi, 1970-1971 (Box 20)
      - Book III, 1971; 3 folders (Box 20)
      - Book IV, 1971-1973; 3 folders (Box 20)
      - Book NIV: Recombinant Equine x Swine, Equine Pr8, 954 Sera, SAFB, Ypsilanti and Lapeer, 1973-1974; 3 folders (Box 21)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2072 ]
      - Book V: Intranasal Vaccine X-15 and A-15 (HK), 1970-1972; 3 folders (Box 21)
      - Book NVI: New Recombinants, 1971-1972 (Box 21)
      - NVII: Miscellaneous B and Equine Neuraminidase, 1973-1974 (Box 21)
      - NI tests of PR8 Virus, 1971-1972; 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Neuraminidase Ferret Experiment, 1975 (Box 21)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2075 ]
      - Neuraminidase Standardizations, 1976 (Box 21)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2076 ]
      - Neuraminidase Activity and Inhibition Book II, 1977 (Box 21)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2077 ]
      - NI, 1979 (Box 21)
      - NI Current, 1981-1983 (Box 21)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1 2083 ]
    - Ferret Experiments
      - Books I-VIII, XVI, 1972-1977; 3 folders (Box 21)
      - Books 35 and 36, 1986-1987; 2 folders (Box 22)
      - Book 37, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Books, 1989-1997; 4 folders (Box 22)
      - Ferret Experiment Attenuated Strains, 1975 (Box 22)
      - Ferret Results, undated (Box 22)
      - Various Summaries of Ferret Data, 1976-1990; undated (Box 22)
      - Single Gene Ferret Experiment, Type A Influenza from Mark Snyder (NIH), 1984-1985 (Box 22)
    - Viruses
      - Various Viruses, 1973-1979; 1975-1977; 2 folders (Box 22)
      - AA/CR18, AA/CR24 and AA/CR26, 1974-1982; 2 volumes (Box 22)
      - AA/CR33-AA/CR36, 1977-1978; 2 volumes (Box 22)
      - AA/CR37 and AA/CR39, 1979 (Box 22)
      - AA/CR37-AA/CR55, 1978-1979; 2 folders (Box 23)
      - AA/CR56-AA/CRB67, 1982-1984 (Box 23)
      - AA/CRB68-AA/CR82, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
      - AA/CR83-AA/CR121, 1985-1986; 2 folders (Box 23)
      - AA/CRB106-AA/CRB115 and AA/CRB122-AA/CRB123, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
      - AA/CR124-AA/CR143, 1986-1987 (Box 23)
      - AA/CR144-AA/CR158, 1987-1988 (Box 23)
      - AA/CR159-AA/CR173, 1989-1990 (Box 23)
      - AA/CR 174-AA/CR193, 1991-1992 (Box 23)
      - AA/CRB194-AA/CR207, 1992-1994 (Box 23)
      - AA/CR208-AA/CR226, 1995-1996; 2 folders (Box 23)
      - A/AA/2/85, C/AA/1/50 and Assorted Non-SPAFAS Virus Pools, 1985-1993 (Box 23)
    - Egg Books
      - SPAFAS Books 1-6 and 8-10, 1976-1997 (Box 23)
      - Sue Peters' Egg Pools Book 1, 1986-1987 (Box 23)
    - Hardcover Bound Books
      - AA/CR 22 Clones, 1976-1977 (Box 24)
      - AA/CR 23 Clones, 1977-1978 (Box 24)
      - AA/CR 24 Clones, 1977 (Box 24)
      - AA/CR 37 Clones, 1979 (Box 24)
      - AA/CR 33 -- AA/CR 36; A/USSR/90/77; A/HK/123/77, 1978-1979 (Box 24)
      - AA/CR 28 -- AA/CR 31, 1977-1978 (Box 24)
      - AA/CR 13 -- Clone 5; A/Dunedin/4/73, 1978-1979 (Box 24)
      - AA/CR B50; AA/CR 51 -- AA/CR 55, 1981-1982 (Box 24)
      - AA/CR 43 -- AA/CR B46, 1979-1981 (Box 24)
      - AA/CR 47 -- AA/CR 49 (Box 24)
      - NIH, 1981 (Box 24)
      - Houston; NIH; Kendal; Flow Studies, 1979-1980 (Box 24)
      - Cold Attenuated RSV, 1977-1990 (Box 24)
    - Duphar Vaccines1977-1987, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Respiratory Syncytial Virus (RSV) Research
      - 3-ring Binder, 1976-1978 (Box 25)
      - Para RSV: HeLa and MDCK, 1983 (Box 25)
      - 3-ring Binder, 1991 (Box 25)
      - 4 Notepads on RSV, 1992-1994 (Box 25)
      - 3-ring Binder, 1993-1995 (Box 25)
      - Lab Book, 1993-1996 (Box 25)
      - Lab Book, 1997-1999 (Box 25)
      - Miscellaneous, 1994-1995 (Box 25)
      - Vaccina Vector with RSV, 1998-1999 (Box 25)
    - Genotyping and Sequencing
      - Genotyping Gels Binder 1, 1982-1983 (Box 25)
      - Type B 'Master Strains" Biochemistry, 1984 (Box 25)
      - S. Powell's Genotyping Notebooks XIII-XV, 1991-1995 (Box 25)
      - Sue Peters' (Donabedian's) Sequencing Notebooks I-III, 1985-1989 (Box 25)
      - Genotyping Colony Counts, 1993-1994 (Box 25)
      - Sequencing of B/AA/1/66 and B/AA/5/66, 1993-1995 (Box 25)
      - Sequencing of A/AA/6/60, B/AA/1/66 and B/AA/5/66, 1995-1996 (Box 25)
      - Genotype Films
        - A/AA/1/93, undated (Box 26)
        - A/AA/3/93, undated (Box 26)
        - A/AA/6/60, undated (Box 26)
        - A/AA/6/60-Cold Adapted, undated (Box 26)
        - A/AA/9/95; CR 223 and CR 224, undated (Box 26)
        - A/Argentina/3779/94 and AA/CR 213, undated (Box 26)
        - A/Kaw/9/86 Reassortants, undated (Box 26)
        - AA/LA/2/87 and CR 149, undated (Box 26)
        - A/Lenzhow/1/95 and CR 226, undated (Box 26)
        - A/Mallard/NY/78 and HR-R 205, undated (Box 26)
        - A/PR/8, undated (Box 26)
        - A/Quizhou/54/89, undated (Box 26)
        - A/Shanghai/16/89, undated (Box 26)
        - A/Shongdong/9/93, undated (Box 26)
        - A/Texas/36/91, undated (Box 26)
        - A/Wuhan/359/96, undated (Box 26)
        - A/Yamagata/32/89, undated (Box 26)
        - AA/CR 173 Equine, undated (Box 26)
        - AA/CR 176 Equine, undated (Box 26)
        - AA/CR 179 Beijing, undated (Box 26)
        - B/AA/1/86 Reassortants, undated (Box 26)
        - B/AA/1/94, undated (Box 26)
        - B/Bangkok/163/90, undated (Box 26)
        - B/California/1/95 and CRB 220, undated (Box 26)
        - B/CAN Reassortants; CRB 102-105, undated (Box 26)
        - B/Haiben/7/94 and CRB 221, undated (Box 26)
        - B/Panama/45/90, undated (Box 26)
        - B/Qingdao/102/91, undated (Box 26)
        - B/Vic/2/87 Reassortants, undated (Box 26)
        - B/Yamagata/16/88 Reassortants, undated (Box 26)
        - CR18-CR19, CR22, undated; 2 folders (Box 26)
        - CR29, undated (Box 26)
        - CR31, undated (Box 26)
        - CR43-CR45, undated; 3 folders (Box 26)
        - CR47-CR48, undated; 2 folders (Box 26)
        - CRB50-CR51, undated; 2 folders (Box 26)
        - CR55 and MDI, undated (Box 26)
        - CR59, undated (Box 26)
        - CRB60, undated (Box 26)
        - CR62, undated (Box 26)
        - CR64, undated (Box 26)
        - CR66, undated (Box 26)
        - CRB68, undated (Box 26)
        - CR69-CR71, undated; 2 folders (Box 26)
        - CRB76-CRB81, undated; 6 folders (Box 26)
        - CR82, undated (Box 27)
        - CR85-CRB87, undated; 3 folders (Box 27)
        - CR90, undated (Box 27)
        - CR92-CR98, undated; 7 folders (Box 27)
        - CR131 and CR132, undated; 2 folders (Box 27)
        - CRB 134-CRB137, undated; 2 folders (Box 27)
        - CR 140, undated (Box 27)